hello this is the first in a series of
videos I'm gonna be releasing over the
next couple of weeks to explain why we
are creating a technology cooperative
and what that can do for us
as a individual as a society as a globe
what we can accomplish together right
now in our lives technology's already
powerful there's four main companies
that owner eyeballs owner attention on
the gadgets that we choose to be on they
are Amazon
with a hundred and thirty four billion
dollars and a hundred million Prime
subscribers that's not all the people
who use Amazon those are just the ones
who pay for the free shipping and
streaming video there are a hundred and
four billion dollars under the hands of
Facebook with 2.8 billion users Google
102 billion dollars with two trillion
searches a year Apple 80 billion with 1
billion people choosing to use their
devices roughly 1.4 billion products
this is being recorded on an Apple
product there's a reason they've gotten
to be so powerful and it's said they've
given us something of value
they've connected us informed us
empowered us and made our lives cheaper
and more convenient but that has also
come at a cost we are their commodity
they are selling our data and our
attention and our connections to
advertisers and that is making us more
addicted they're making their decisions
for profit because they're playing game
a there's no question about it we can
create a technology company that's based
on cooperation that meets our needs for
less and less and less money and puts us
in power of our data so this is the
first in a series of videos that's going
to explore why we are starting with tech
what we can create together and why what
we are gonna create together they can't
compete with this those are huge numbers
do you even think you can compete with
them become the new Amazon the new
Facebook the new Google the new Apple
we're gonna become them all because
we're gonna start small and we are going
to keep improving and keep inviting more
people we don't start competing with
them on any level but as we add people
as we add our own dad
as we add our human ingenuity to the
collaboration to voluntary cooperation
there comes a point where they can't
compete with us because they're they're
working for profit and we're working for
purpose and people are ready to work
towards purpose so please like and
subscribe a better world is on its way
stay tuned for more